# **David Zuñiga**

San José, Costa Rica

+506 8327 4231 jdavid.zunigar@gmail.com https://davezuniga.github.io/portfolio/ www.spaceweb.dev

## **ABOUT ME**

I would introduce myself in six words.

Passionate coder, responsible, best colleague ever. That pretty much sums it up, though at least the last one my former colleagues have to confirm. I try to do a good job in all roles I have in life, and I enjoy the process immensely. Do you want me to talk about my coding skills and experience now, or will we discuss it later in the interview?

#### **COMPETENCIES**

- Python
- SQL
- Google Cloud
- Airflow
- JavaScript
- Data Analytics
- · Cyber security
- Jenkins

## **LANGUAGES**

- English, Full Professional Proficiency.
- · Spanish, Native.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **IBM**

- Technical Support Agent Apr 2019 to Nov 2019
- Backlog dispatcher lead: Manage L1 account backlog,
- Backlog data analysis using Python and reporting.
- Coordinate with different teams to work on new issues, priorities and special cases.
  - Centralize Technical Agent Nov 2019 to Feb 2021

Support to physical and virtual machines (Citrix) and servers (Azure and Google cloud) and configuration automation using Puppet.

- Backlog data analysis using service now, Python and MS Excel.

## Server Engineer

Avid/CSS - February 2021 to Aug 2021

- Provide support to English speaking users on issues with Avid production management tools and their functionality on Windows and Linux servers.
- Log analysis, tasks automation with Python and management and automation with Terraform and Jenkins.

# **Cloud Automation Engineer**

Equifax - Aug 2021 to present

- GCp and AWS task automation with Python, terraform, bash and data analysis with
- Google Big Query and, AirFlow

## **EDUCATION**

## **CENFOTEC**

- Infrastructure and IT superior technical degree.
- Front-end web Development Certification.
- ECCouncil Certified Ethical Hacker Certification.
- IT bachelor's degree.

## Coursera

- IBM Cybersecurity Analyst Professional Certificate.
- Google IT Automation with Python Professional Certificate.
- Jenkins Automating your delivery pipeline.
- IBM AI Engineering Professional Certificate (Python).
- Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate.